[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Chunk from the movie The Goonies is locked up with scary Sloth he throws what kind of candy bar at him?", "correct_answer": "Baby Ruth", "incorrect_answers": ["Hersey Bar", "Snickers", "Milky Way"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of rice is used for the preparation of the traditional Vietnamese dish Com tam?", "correct_answer": "Broken rice", "incorrect_answers": ["Brown rice", "Long rice", "Coarsely ground rice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the official language that is spoken in North Korea?", "correct_answer": "Korean", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Russian", "Japanese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was the letter e\u201d chosen to denote the important mathematical constant e?", "correct_answer": "It stands for exponential.", "incorrect_answers": ["It was arbitrarily chosen by Latin scholars.", "Its the first letter of a mathematicians name.", "The first 4 letters of the alphabet were already taken."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If I were to visit the wrist-wrestling capital of the world, where would I go?", "correct_answer": "Petaluma, California.", "incorrect_answers": ["Riga, Latvia", "Sofia, Bulgaria", "Norman, Oklahoma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many men held the title King of England in 1936?", "correct_answer": "3 -  George V, Edward VIII, and George VI", "incorrect_answers": ["1 - George V", "2 -  Albert II and George VI", "0 - There was a queen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a sign of power, wealth and success.", "correct_answer": "Dragon", "incorrect_answers": ["Horse", "Tiger", "Rooster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "US Army Lt. Thomas Selfridge was the first person killed in a powered fixed-wing aircraft. Where did the accident happen?", "correct_answer": "Virginia", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Colorado", "Pennsylvania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1980s film, The Hitcher, starring Rutger Hauer and Jennifer Jason-Leigh, was shot in the same location as which other film?", "correct_answer": "Welcome to Serendipity", "incorrect_answers": ["Hot Moon", "Baghdad Cafe", "Death Valley Days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these watch companies has produced luxury watches under the Calvin Klein brand?", "correct_answer": "Swatch", "incorrect_answers": ["Rolex", "Seiko", "Casio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Larb meat salad belongs to the cuisine of what Asian country?", "correct_answer": "Laos", "incorrect_answers": ["Cambodia", "India", "China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What led to the incredible increase in U.S. sales of popcorn in the 1990s?", "correct_answer": "Availability of microwaves", "incorrect_answers": ["Increased sales of soda pop", "Food shortages", "Lower prices"]}]